http://www.dominator.co.nz/privacy-policy/

COVID-19 Update: We continue to offer our full range of services while meeting government guidelines. Virtual Consultations may also be available, talk to your local Dominator Dealer to find out more.
Home
Garage Doors
Steel Sectional Doors
Insulated Sectional Doors
Designer Garage Doors
Rolling Doors
Flex-A-Door
Tilting Doors
Company History
Why Dominator?
Our Easy 5 Step Process
Gallery
Dominator Colour Options
Dominator Inspiration Gallery
Resources
Brochures
Sectional Panel Styles
Colour Options
Our commitment to protect your privacy
In your relationship with us, you may share information with us. This information may include your name, address, telephone numbers, email address, bank account and credit card details, date of birth and other personal details in connection with transactions entered into by you with us.
We recognise the importance of your privacy and how important it is for us to protect your personal information. We are committed to protecting personal information which we hold and to complying with all relevant privacy laws in the jurisdictions in which we operate. This document describes how we manage your personal information and safeguard your privacy.
How do we collect and hold personal information about you?
We will only collect personal information that is necessary for us to carry on our business; to provide the products and services our customers require; let our customers know about other products and/or services which might interest them; and to assist us generally in managing transactions with our customers, suppliers, consumers and other contacts with us.
The kinds of personal information we collect and hold will depend upon the type of products and services we provide to you or obtain from you. It may be contained in:
information you give us when you request a product or service from us or enter a competition of ours;
credit related information necessary to assess applications for credit and personal guarantees;
records of communications between us and you; and
if you have or had one of our products, information about the use of that product or your opinions about that product recorded when you respond to a survey.
The personal information we request is optional, but if you choose not to provide personal information to us, we may not be able to fulfil your request or provide you with the product or service you require. Sometimes, however, there are situations where we are required by law to collect certain personal information from you and, if this is the case, we will inform you of the law that imposes this requirement.
We will collect personal information directly from you whenever it is reasonable practicable to do so. We may, at times, also collect personal information from other parties such as other members of the DuluxGroup (except where you tell us not to), credit reporting and collection agencies, unrelated third parties as well as from your agents or representatives (such as your legal or financial adviser) and from publicly available sources of information.
Where personal information is used for credit reporting purposes in association with an Application for Credit the agency that collects and holds that personal information for credit reporting purposes is Veda Advantage NZ Limited.Veda Advantage NZ Limited can be contacted at Private Bag 92156, Auckland Mail Centre, Auckland 1142, or on www.mycreditfile.co.nz.
What do we do with the personal information we collect?
We respect your privacy. Any personal information which we collect about you will only be used and disclosed for the purposes for which it is collected or for related purposes and will not be used or disclosed outside of the DuluxGroup without your consent, except where described in this privacy policy.
We may use and file personal information you provide when dealing with us to assist us in providing you with our products and services and/or information which may be of interest to you. For example, another member of the DuluxGroup of companies may contact you by telephone, mail, electronically or otherwise to provide you with marketing or other information on its products and services or follow up on your interest in particular products and services, unless or until you tell us not to. We may also disclose your personal information to market research agencies, who may contact you in a similar manner to conduct market research in relation to products and services you have acquired from or are offered by the DuluxGroup and related matters (unless or until you tell us not to).
In order to do this, we disclose your personal information to those employees or advisers who need to know that information to assist us in providing you with our range of products and services.
We may also disclose information to affiliates, contractors and service providers and other third parties necessary to process your transactions, service your account and provide you with the products and services you request (including our print service providers, call centres and mail houses, advertising agencies, our accountants, auditors and lawyers and credit reporting and collection agencies) (together, "Third Parties"). These Third Parties may use your personal information for their own business purposes, including for example, a credit reporter using your personal information to update its credit reporting database and disclosing your personal information to any of its customers who use their credit reporting database. We may also disclose your personal information in corporate transactions involving the transfer of all or part of our assets or business or in a corporate restructure. If we do this, we generally require these parties to protect your information in the same way we do.
We may also be required or authorised by law to disclose your personal information. For example, we may disclose your personal information to a court in response to a subpoena or to a relevant taxation agency. We may also disclose information to other persons where you have provided your consent to do so.
Personal information collected by us may be stored and processed in any country in which we maintain facilities, but will continue to be subject to the terms of this privacy policy.
Once we no longer require your personal information for any of the purposes for which it was collected we will, subject to any legal obligations and responsibilities, take reasonable steps to destroy or de-identify your personal information.
How do we protect your personal information?
We take all reasonable steps to protect your personal information from loss, misuse, modification, or unauthorised access, use and disclosure. These steps include access control for our buildings, confidentiality obligations imposed on our employees and use of security measures for computer system access. We do not, however, accept any responsibility for the unauthorised access, use or disclosure of personal information held by us.
Your privacy on our websites
This privacy policy also applies to the websites operated by us under various domain names. We operate websites which may utilise ‘cookies' tracking pixels and related technologies to collect personal information. A cookie is a small file that is stored on your hard disk by a website. Cookies contain information which is readable by the website that issued the cookie to you. Our site uses cookies dropped by us or third parties for a variety of purposes including to operate and personalise the website. Also, cookies may also be used to track how you use the site to target ads to you on other websites. Cookies cannot execute programs or access other information on your computer. Your web browser can be configured to reject cookies issued by our websites, but if you do so, some functionality that we provide on our websites may become unavailable as a result.
If you transact electronically with another member of the DuluxGroup, you should refer to the website of that member for more information on its website privacy and security procedures.
When you visit a website of ours, we may collect the following information from you: your name, information you volunteer such as survey information, email addresses and IP address.
While we take care that the personal information you give us on our websites is protected, the Internet is not a secure environment. If you send us information, including your email address, it is sent at your own risk.
If you provide your email address, telephone number, address or other personal information to us, it may be used by us and other members of the DuluxGroup to provide you with marketing or other information relating to our products and services or follow up on your interest in particular products and services. If you do not wish to receive marketing emails from the DuluxGroup in the future, please notify us or the relevant DuluxGroup business.
You may be able to access external websites, operated by companies unrelated to us, by clicking on links we have provided. Those other websites are not subject to our privacy standards and we are not responsible for their privacy practices or the content of such other websites. You should contact those websites directly to ascertain their privacy standards, policies and procedures.
What rights do you have in relation to your personal information which we hold?
We take all reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we collect, use and disclose is accurate, complete and up-to-date. If you become aware of any errors in your personal information or you change your personal details such as your name, address or bank account details, you should contact us as soon as possible.
In most cases, you can gain access to personal information that we hold about you, subject to certain exceptions allowed by law. You can contact our Privacy Officer if you would like details of your personal information which we may hold or if you would like us to correct it. We will handle any request in accordance with the relevant privacy regulations. We may require you to complete a request form and we also reserve the right to charge a reasonable fee for gaining access. We will deal with requests as quickly as possible, but requests for a large amount of information, or information which is not currently in use, may require significant time to extract.
Generally, if you request us to do so we will amend any personal information about you held by us which is inaccurate, incomplete or out of date. If we disagree with you about the accuracy, completeness or currency of personal information held by us, you may request that we associate with that information a statement to the effect that you claim that the information is not accurate, complete or up to date. If we are not able to provide you with access to any personal information or refuse to correct any personal information held by us, we will provide you with reasons.
You may also contact our Privacy Officer to request us to stop using your personal information to contact you about our products and services. If you no longer conduct business with us, you can ask us to remove your personal information. You can contact our Privacy Officer if you wish to obtain more information about the way we manage personal information about you which we hold; or if you are concerned that we may have breached your privacy and wish to make a complaint. If you make a complaint, we will use reasonable endeavours to resolve your complaint as quickly as possible.
Our Privacy Officer can be contacted by calling +64 3 384 5145.
Changes to this privacy statement
We may change our privacy policies from time to time to comply with new laws or industry codes of practice which are developed or to align with changes to our business. It is your responsibility to refer to our privacy policies from time to time to familiarise yourself with any changes. We encourage you to visit our websites regularly for any updates to our privacy policies.
Last Updated: 1 August 2011
Prepared by the Company Secretary© 2015 B&D Doors (NZ) Ltd.
Join our newsletter
Submit
Contact Info
GalleryContact UsOur Trading TermsSite MapMeasure & QuoteService & RepairsOur Website RulesYour PrivacyPromotion
Products
Garage Doors
Openers
Industrial
Resources
Repairs
Warranty
About Us
About UsCompany HistoryWhy Dominator?Our Easy 5 Step Process
Resources
BrochuresSectional Panel StylesColour OptionsDominator BlogFAQsChoosing the Right Garage DoorSafetyDoor Care & MaintenanceOwner's ManualsFraming Details
Contact Info
Find a Dealer
call us on 0800 366 462
info@dominator.co.nz
YouTube
Google +
Facebook
Products
About Us
About UsCompany HistoryWhy Dominator?Our Easy 5 Step Process
Resources
BrochuresSectional Panel StylesColour OptionsDominator BlogFAQsChoosing the Right Garage DoorSafetyDoor Care & MaintenanceOwner's ManualsFraming Details
Site Designed and Developed by 72DPI
Copyright © 2020 Dominator
| All Rights Reserved
GalleryContact UsOur Trading TermsSite MapMeasure & QuoteService & RepairsOur Website RulesYour PrivacyPromotion Site Designed and Developed by 72DPI
This website uses cookies to optimise your experience. By continuing to use our website you are agreeing to our Privacy Policy.
Accept and close this alert or
Read Privacy Policy
